targetsportsusa.com 2013-05-20

# Privacy Policy Details | Target Sports USA.com

###  TargetSportsUSA.com Privacy Policy

This privacy identifies what personal information we collect when you visit our website, what choices you can make about your personal information, how we use this data, and how we protect your personal information. 

TargetSportsUSA.com respects your privacy, and we will do our best to earn and keep your trust. All personal information that you share with us is treated with the utmost cares. TargetSportsUSA.com has created this policy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to the privacy of all our Customers nationwide.

### What is Covered by This Policy?

This Privacy Policy applies to website operated by Delmic Enterprise LLC and its Affiliates nationwide. The purpose of this policy is to tell our Customers what information we collect, how it is used, where it is used and how to contact TargetSportsUSa.com with privacy inquiries. 

### Information We Collect and How We Use It

TargetSportsUSA.com collects information, including personal information, which you provide to us when you visit our website. Personal information includes information that can identify you such as your full name, your e-mail address or postal address, birth date, payment details, product references and purchasing history. 

TargetSportsUSA.com collects and uses your personal information to conduct business with you and to improve your experience with us. Some examples include: 

  * Making an online purchase 
  * Creating a wish list 
  * Processing, fulfilling and following up on online purchases 
  * Creating and maintaining accounts 
  * Registering for our Affiliate program 
  * Handling customer service requests 
  * Sending surveys 
  * Registering to receive email and direct mail 
  * Applying for a job   

### Your Choices and Access to Your Information

Our email, website and other interactive programs allow you to choose to receive or to stop receiving communications from us. You can choose to receive e-mail and/or postal mail from TargetSportsUSA.com

Once you opt out, you are opted out of that type of communication and that brand until we are explicitly told in writing to opt you back in. You may opt out of email programs at any time by following the opt-out instructions provided in the email you receive. You also may be removed from TargetSportsUSA.com program you enrolled in, stop receiving postal mail and other communications, review, update or correct your information, or prevent any further use of your personal information by TargetSportsUSA.com by contacting us. TargetSportsUSA.com will respond to reasonable requests in an appropriate time frame as determined by the respective authority.  

### Sharing Information with Third Parties

TargetSportsUSA.com does not release the personally identifiable information it collects from you to any unrelated third parties so that they may send you commercial promotions or offers for products or services. We do, however, share anonymous, aggregate information concerning the demographic makeup of our customers to unrelated third parties, and share personal information as described below: 

### Affiliates and Franchisees

We may disclose information (including Personally Identifiable Information) collected from guests outside of the US to affiliated companies or “Affiliates” in the US and elsewhere. For purposes of this Privacy Policy, "Affiliates" means any person or entity which directly or indirectly controls, is controlled by or is under common control with TargetSportsUSA.com, whether by ownership or otherwise. Any information relating to you that we provide to our Affiliates will be treated by those Affiliates in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy. We may share your information (including Personally Identifiable Information) with franchisees of TargetSportsUSA.com  but only where we indicate to you at time of information collection that such information will be provided to a franchisee, or if we otherwise obtain your permission. 

### Business Transfers

TargetSportsUSA.com reserves the right to transfer your personal information in connection with the sale or transfer of all or a portion of our business or assets. If the business is sold or transferred, TargetSportsUSA.com will give you an opportunity to tell us not to transfer your personal information. In some cases, this may mean that the new organization will not be able to continue providing you with the services or products that TargetSports.com provided. 

### Service Providers

Further, we may share your information with our service providers—that is, organizations providing services to support TargetSportsUSA.com functions, such as our mail and email processing companies, payment processing companies, and market research firms. All such service providers are bound by contract to refrain from using the personally identifiable information we collect from you for any purpose other than providing the service to TargetSportsUSA.com.

### Laws and Legal Rights

We also may release information at the request of law enforcement authorities, when ordered to do so by a court, or when we have the right to do so and believe it is necessary to assert or protect our legal or intellectual property rights. 

### Fraud Prevention

In order to protect our Guests and ourselves from fraud or theft, we may pass information to other organizations (including law enforcement agencies).  

### Information Transfer

When TargetSportsUSA.com transfers personal information to countries other than the country where it was provided, we do so in compliance with applicable data protection laws. All Guest personal information is transmitted to our headquarters in Cromwell, Connecticut daily. No copies of the data exist at the point of origin. We may transfer personal information from guests outside the US to Affiliates located either in the US or otherwise. In order to provide for adequate protection of your personal information, we have in place contractual arrangements with our Affiliates.  

### Information Security

TargetSportsUSA.com maintains reasonable security measures, such as firewall, limited access, and SSL encryption technology, designed to help protect against loss, misuse, and alteration of Guest information collected by TargetSportsUSA.com. 

### Passive Data Collection – Cookies and Web Beacons

TargetSportsUSA.com website may also collect information passively, through the use of cookies. A cookie is a small text file that writes to your hard drive. The cookie file contains your computer's IP address and a user ID. The user ID links any orders you have placed on our site to your personal information. A user ID has no personally identifiable information attached to it unless you place an order on our site. Our website uses cookies to enhance the Guests’ experience and help us improve our services. For example, we may use cookies to keep track of your basket or shopping cart while you are shopping on our site or to track your activity. TargetSportsUSA.com uses web beacons in emails to track traffic from the email to specific pages on our websites. You may be able to adjust your browser so that your computer either does not accept cookies, or notifies you when a website tries to deposit a cookie into your computer. Our cookies do not contain confidential information such as your home address, telephone number, or credit card information. We do not exchange cookies with any third parties.  

### Changes to This Privacy Statement

We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time. If we make any changes in the way we collect, use, and/or share your personal information, we will notify you by sending you an e-mail at the last e-mail address that you provided us, or by prominently posting notice of the changes on the web sites covered by this Privacy Policy. 

### Contact Us

If you have questions or concerns regarding your privacy, please contact TargetSportsUSA.com directly. Please feel free to use your native language when sending your questions or comments. 

**In the US and Canada:**

Information Officer  
TargetSportsUSA.com  
504 Main Street  
Farmington, CT 06032  
Email: info@targetsportsusa.com  
Telephone: 1-800-511-8220

* * *

**Popular Hunting Supply & Shooting  Categories  
**

[Hunting Optics](http://targetsportsusa.com/c-206-scopes-accessories.aspx) |  [Hunting Binoculars](http://targetsportsusa.com/c-522-binoculars.aspx) | [Black Hills Ammunition](http://targetsportsusa.com/m-30-black-hills-ammunition.aspx) | [Hunting Rifle Scopes](http://targetsportsusa.com/c-611-rifle-scopes.aspx) | [Gun Sights](http://targetsportsusa.com/c-539-laser-sights.aspx) | [Magazines](http://targetsportsusa.com/c-36-magazines-clips.aspx) | [Blank Ammunition](http://targetsportsusa.com/c-31-blank-ammunition.aspx)[ ](http://targetsportsusa.com/c-31-blank-ammunition.aspx)| [Range Bags   
](http://targetsportsusa.com/c-554-bags.aspx)

**Popular Ammunition Manufacturers**
